http://www.iftn.ie/privacy_securitypolicy/

Actors
ActorsTVCrewDigitalDistributionEducation / Training EquipmentFestivals / MarketsFinanceLegalLocations IrelandPost ProductionProductionRep Bodies
IFTN HOME
SECURITY & PRIVACY POLICY OF IFTN.ieSECURITY POLICYSECURITYYou can feel confident when buying online with IFTN. That's because we ensure the safety of the personal and billing information you use when making a purchase. SAFE TECHNOLOGYOur secure server software (SSL) is among the best software available today for secure commerce transactions. It encrypts all your personal information for protection so nobody else can gain access to it.CREDIT CARD PROTECTIONWhen you purchase online, credit card purchases are generally protected against fraud by law, and your liability is limited. Check with your credit card company for details. Be aware that improvements in technology have significantly decreased any chance of Internet credit card fraud.INFORMATION WE COLLECTNon-Personal (Aggregated) Information IFTN.ie gathers information on all users of our site on an aggregated basis. This information is used to analyse what the total usage levels are for the site, what areas of the site are most popular and what times of the day are most popular for using the site. This information is used to determine what improvements we can make going forward. In addition, we may share this information with our clients or potential clients and our partners, but only on an aggregated basis with no individual breakdown, so they receive no information about how you, as an individual, use the site, nor will they be able to identify you personally from the information they receive. Personal InformationThere are areas of the IFTN.ie website where you can request information, subscribe to marketing materials, enter competitions, register yourself for our online services, request customer support or apply for a job within our organisation. This can involve registering your personal information such as; your name, e-mail address, contact details, credits, company information. The information collected is solely for the purpose of personalising your user experience and for delivering the service(s) that you have signed up for. Once you choose to provide IFTN.ie with personal information, you can be certain that it will only be used to support your relationship with us.PRIVACY POLICYThis Privacy Policy applies to the IFTN.ie owned website and domain.The IFTN.ie website may provide links to third-party websites for your convenience. If you access these links, you will leave the IFTN.ie website. IFTN.ie does not control these sites or their privacy practices. Any exchange of information with unrelated third parties is not covered by this Privacy Policy.We encourage all users to review the Privacy Policy/statement of any third party before submitting personal information.COPYRIGHT STATEMENTDisclaimer for IFTN Web-site This site and the contents herein are intended for personal use only.Copyright in all material contained in the IFTN web-site is owned by or licensed to IFTN and all rights in the same are reserved, including but not limited to content, text, photographs, graphics, software, site titles, layout and site specific user interface. Neither this website nor any site content may be displayed in public, published, copied, reproduced, stored in any medium (including any other website), distributed, transmitted, retransmitted, modified, used for the creation of derivative works, or used for any commercial purpose whatsoever without the express written permission of IFTN, First Floor, Palmerstown Centre, Kennelsfort Road, Dublin 20. Furthermore, the unauthorised framing, selling on, or any other use or reproduction of material from this web-site is a breach of the rights of IFTN.Every effort has been made to ensure the accuracy of our service and of the information contained in this site. However, IFTN makes no representations or warranties about the content and suitability of the information contained herein for any purpose. IFTN disclaims all liability for the accuracy, completeness or usefulness of any information contained herein and does not accept responsibility for any errors or omissions. Liability is also disclaimed for negligence and for any claims, penalities, damages, expenses whatsoever resulting from loss of use, data or profits arising out of or in connection with the viewing, use or performance of this website or its contents or from any unauthorised access to or alteration of the same.Links to the IFTN web-site are not permitted other than to the Home Page and such links require the express consent of IFTNCOPYRIGHT NOTICE© 2008 IFTN ALL RIGHTS RESERVED (IFTN is a registered trading company of Irish Film Research Ltd)Copyright in the whole and every part of this web-site belongs to IFTN and the said site may not be used, sold, licensed, transferred, copied or reproduced, in whole or in part, in any manner or form, or in or on any media, to any person, without either the prior written consent of, or a formal agreement from the said IFTN.Copyright in all material contained in this website (including but not limited to text, photographs, graphics, software, contents, site titles, layout and site specific user interface) is owned by or licensed to IFTN and all rights in the same are reserved. Neither this website, nor site content may be displayed in public, copied, published, reproduced, stored in any medium (including any other website), distributed, transmitted, retransmitted, modified, used for the creation of derivative works or used for any commercial purpose whatsoever without the express written permission of IFTN and Irish Film Research Ltd. Furthermore, the unauthorised framing, selling on or any other use or reproduction of material from this website is a breach of that copyright. The Licensee acknowledges the rights of IFTN as outlined herein.CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICYIFTN reserves the right to change or remove this Privacy Policy at its discretion and will post any new Privacy Policy here. Therefore we would encourage you to visit this area frequently to stay informed.CONTACT INFORMATIONIFTN welcomes any comments regarding this Privacy Policy. If you have reason to believe that IFTN has not adhered to this Privacy Policy, please contact us or write to us at the address provided below; and we will make all reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.1st Floor, Palmerstown Centre, Kennelsfort Road, Dublin 20, Ireland.T: + 353 1 6200811  F: + 353 1 6200810
the Website
Directory List
Festivals
Who's Who
Locations
Filmography
News
Crew
